THAO THI NGUYEN

- Thao.Nguyen-1@colorado.edu
- h (720) 292-0540
- a Boulder, CO 80302

SKILLS

- Self-regulating and reliable
- Real estate industry knowledge
- Detail-oriented
- Market research and analysis
- Excellent communication skills
- Proficient in Microsoft Applications: Excel, PowerPoint and Word
- Manage multiple priorities
- Team collaboration & leadership
- Adaptable to new work environments

EDUCATION

University of Colorado Boulder Boulder, CO • Expected in 2021

Bachelor of Science: Business Administration And Information Analytics

- Real Estate Certificate
- Cumulative GPA: 3.567
- CU Boulder Impact Scholars Scholarship

University of NSW Sydney, Australia

Study Abroad Spring 2020

LEADERSHIP

Pi Beta Phi Sorority, Boulder, CO Health and Nutrition Committee (Member since Fall 2017)

 Promoted mindfulness and health benefits of yoga to 60 members through event partnership with Bulldog Yoga

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Self-motivated student in Information Analytics attaining a Real Estate Certificate who has put herself through College, learning to overcome any barrier to attain success. Strong interest in the Real Estate Industry. Prepared to contribute abilities to a company while further developing acquired skills and gaining real-world experience. Highly organized, demonstrating history of attention to detail, strategic planning, critical thinking and ability to successfully work with a diverse group of individuals.

WORK HISTORY

Compass Real Estate - Intern Wynnewood, PA • 04/2020 - 05/2020

- Analyzed social media campaigns and activities using Instagram and Facebook to promote engagement and made recommendations for enhancement as company transitions to online marketing during COVID-19 pandemic
- Fostered collaborative efforts to schedule, host and facilitate events and identify further opportunities to reach members of the community while respecting the 'stay-at-home' order
- Increased data-entry productivity by maintaining detailed logs of client information

Self Employed - Eyelash Technician Boulder, CO • 08/2017 - Current

- Built clientele network through direct referrals, maintaining 80% client retention rate
- Conduct competitive analysis against local companies with objective to set high-end service pricing
- Providing eyelash extensions to eight clients weekly, maintaining professional setting following sanitation and sterilization State Law procedures
- Develop, update and maintain clientele database to track appointments optimizing booking system

Magic Salon - Marketing Intern Lone Tree, CO • 05/2019 - 08/2019

- Designed, presented and implemented flyer marketing campaign resulting in increase of 100 customers per day
- Managed company's Yelp, Facebook, and Instagram which included handling all communication for promotional advertising and customer reviews

Magic Salon - Client Manager Lone Tree, CO • 04/2012 - 04/2017

- Built client relationships by responding to inquiries, identifying and assessing clients' needs, resolving problems, and following up with over 300+ potential and existing clients daily to ensure satisfaction.
- Supervised daily technician operations and sales functions to ensure maximization of revenue, customer satisfaction and employee productivity,